

Ahmed Ferah

Senior Web Developer

Experience: 4 years +

Meantime: Web development Trainer

13/09/1999

Contact

Tel (whatsapp): +216 58411214 E-mail:ahmedferah.dev@gmail.com Linkedin: @ahmed-farah-991965186 Github :https://github.com/hmedhappy Site: https://ahmed-ferah.site

Technologies

























Profil

I am a pragmatic, objective and professional person who adapts easily with people. I am a curious and ambitious worker in all fields and especially in Future Web Technologies

EXPERIENCES PROFESSIONNELLES

- PROJECT MANAGER / LEAD FULLSTACK TYPESCRIPT AT WEREACT Dec 2021 - Maintenant
- SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER FULLSTACK TYPESCRIPT AT WEREACT Juillet 2021 - Maintenant
- SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER FULLSTACK TYPESCRIPT AT OPUS LAB Juin 2021 - Maintenant
- CO-FOUNDER IN OPUS LAB

Juin 2021 - Maintenant

- WEB DEVELOPPEMENT TRAINER (MERN STACK) IN OPUS LAB Oct 2019 - Juin 2021
- FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER (PERN STACK) IN ORENDA JE Orenda Junior Entreprise Dec 2019 - Juin 2021
- WEB DEVELOPER / TEAM LEADER IN ORENDA JUNIOR ENTREPRISE Dec 2018 - Juin 2021
- WEB DEVELOPER IN ORENDA JUNIOR ENTREPRISE Oct 2018 - Aout 2020
- CONSULTANT FINANCE & LEGALITIES & TEAM LEADER IN AIESEC

Oct 2018 - Jan 2019

CERTIFICATS

CERTIFICAT FIRST PRICE HACKATHON: CHALLEN'JE

Sob Flous / Junior Entreprise Oct 2019 - Juin 2021

CERTIFICAT MERN STACK

Training Center Formalab Oct 2019 - Aout 2020

CERTIFICAT FIRST PRICE STARTUP COMPETITION

GoMyCode :/ Université Centrale Sept 2018 - Juillet 2018

CERTIFICAT "YOUTH SPEAK FORUM"

El Space et AIESEC Tunisie Sept 2017- Juillet 2017

EDUCATION

MASTER IN DATA SCIENCE

MASTER IN DATA SCIENCE & BUSINESS COMPUTING 2021 - Now (online)

BACHELOR DEGRES IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

LICENCE FONDAMENTALE EN SCIENCES INFORMATIQUES ET MULTIMEDIA 2018-2021

BACCALAURÉAT| LYCÉE ENNASR 2017-2018

SECTION MATHÉMATIQUES 2017-2018

INTERESTS

- Echec/ Films/ Musique / Basketball

Personnel

Project's

About

· Restoration Marketplace

Name: Quickbill Duration: 6 months • QuickBill: Restaurant management platform where a restaurant owner can create an account and add his points of sale and assign other users as waiter or manager to put the management of the restaurant with integration of the payment service and the services of oracle POS checkout.

Technologies: TypeScript / ReactJs / GraphQL /NodeJS /ExpressJS/ MongoDB / **Tailwind**

• Plateforme Diagoriente.

Name: Fabmap / Diagoriente Duration: 2 years + months

• Diagoriente converted into Fabmap is an online platform for professional doctores. The user finds tools there to become aware that his experiences mobilize skills that can be used to approach the professional world. Technologies: TypeScript / GraphQL / ReactJs / MongoDB / NodeJS

Statistics Management Platform

Name: Piclick Duration: 4 months • Piclick is a click statistics management platform where a user can create an account and put his website and then he can scrape all the images by adding clickable animations to them and thus he can consult the click statistics by page and by animation and per day

MarketPlace B2B Platform & Dashboard Admin

Name: PackShop Duration: 10 months Technologies :TypeScript/GraphQL/ReactJs/Socket.io /NodeJS/ExpressJS/

Advice Website & Stock Management Dashboard

Name: GuideAlize Duration: 11 months · Packshop Smart and interactive marketplace platform for selling products added by suppliers according to their ERP Dashboard. Technologies: TypeScript / NextJS / NodeJS / MongoDB/ Tailwind/graphQL

Educational Website & Stock Management Dashboard

• GuideAlize is a site similar to GuideZephir intended for professional doctors as well as a guide to various diseases with an admin Dashboard for user management. Technologies: TypeScript/GraphQL/ReactJs/Socket.io/NodeJS/ExpressJS/

• Guidezephir is a site intended for professional doctors as well as a guide to chronic

Name: GuideZephir

diseases such as asthma with an admin Dashboard for managing users. Technologies :TypeScript/GraphQL/ReactJs/Socket.io /NodeJS/ExpressJS/

Duration: 1 year + 2 months

MarketPlace B2B Platform & Dashboard Admin

Name: NoomaShop

For: PFE

Duration: 6 months

 NoomaShop Intelligent and interactive marketplace platform for selling products added by suppliers based on their ERP Dashboard Recommendation System - Security - Real Time Statistics

Technologies: ReactJs / Socket.io /NodeJS /ExpressJS/ PostgreSQL

Chat app

Name: SobTchat Duration: 24 hours • SobChat As part of a hackathon that we won the first prize, we designed a chat application in 24 hours where the user can create an account, send an invitation to a friend and chat with.

Points Forts: Sécurity - Modern Design

administrative

Technologies: ReactJs / Socket.io /NodeJS /ExpressJS / MongoDB

ERP Dashboard

Nom: Orenda ERP Duration: 10 months · Dashboard ERP for Junior Enterprise Association which contains Track and Attendance and Video Training applications. Technologies: ReactJs / ExpressJS /NodeJS /GraphQL/ MongoDB

Internship offer platform

Name: Platforme INAT For: Institut Supérieur Agronomique Tunisie

automatic mailing. - Digitization of Paperwork and Facilitation of Workflow

Technologies: ReactJs / ExpressJS /NodeJS / MongoDB

Duration: 1 year + few months

Movie Recommendation Site

Name: HmedMovie

Message Filtering Chrome Extension (Messenger.com)

Name: HmedCheck

• HmedMovie is a site where you can search for movies and see their trailers and then it suggests similar movies to you based on the YouTube API. Integration Highlights: YouTube suggestions API integration based on searches of the user

• Internship offer platform for INAT students where the company creates an internship offer and the student creates an account and completes the form to apply for the

internship then the company studies his profile and CV and accepts it or not with

• HmedCheck Extension for Facebook's Messenger.com site, this extension allows you to filter the messages in your message list and show you only unread messages with the ability to preview the latest messages discreetly without the sender knowing. - Time saving for the user